[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This comedy-drama was written and directed by Woody Allen and was his biggest box office hit.", "correct_answer": "Hannah and Her Sisters", "incorrect_answers": ["Annie Hall", "Mona Lisa", "Lets Get Harry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did Hanna-Barbera produce a Godzilla cartoon series?", "correct_answer": "1978", "incorrect_answers": ["1974", "1964", "1968"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The presence of gallstones in the gallbladder is defined by what medical term?", "correct_answer": "Cholelithiasis", "incorrect_answers": ["Dysentery", "Hepatitis", "Cirrhosis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the young actor who starred in 2006s Civic Duty and whose nicknames include Superman and Dodi.", "correct_answer": "Khaled Abol Naga", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter Krause", "Richard Schiff", "Ian Tracy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1950 book The Martian Chronicles, describing the conflict between the colonists from Earth and the aboriginal Martians, was written by which author?", "correct_answer": "Ray Bradbury", "incorrect_answers": ["Arthur Clarke", "Douglas Adams", "Isaac Asimov"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the color of the legs, bill and eye rims of the Green Magpie, a small Asian bird with bright green plumage?", "correct_answer": "Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Purple", "Blue", "Bright pink"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fear of riding a taxi is referred as epistaxiophobia.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much air do apples contain?", "correct_answer": "1/25", "incorrect_answers": ["1/50", "1/10", "1/75"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Hall of Fame is located in Stillwater, Oklahoma ?", "correct_answer": "National Wrestling Hall of Fame", "incorrect_answers": ["American Track and Field Hall of Fame", "American Softball hall of Fame", "National Museum of College Football"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the song played at the beginning of Rocky IV?", "correct_answer": "Eye of the Tiger", "incorrect_answers": ["Eye of the Lion", "Eye of the Panther", "Eye of the Lizard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Grenada is the real name of the island on which Pirates of the Caribbean was filmed.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the cause of the fire in the movie The Towering Inferno?", "correct_answer": "Faulty electrical wiring", "incorrect_answers": ["Short circuit in the elevator shaft", "A loose lid on a can of kerosene stored in a closet", "Arson"]}]